(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ひばらーに会いたかったので お呼びして 3D LIVE
I wanted to see Hibara-ra, so I invited her for a 3D LIVE
あれ？ママと一緒に影ナレするって聞いたのに...
Wait? I heard I'd be doing the shadow narration with mama...
ここどこや？しかもママどこ？
Where is this? And where is mama?
ママ！ママどこ行ったん？
Mama! Mama, where did you go?
うーん、何も返ってけえへんからなー。
Hmm, since there's no response...
まあ、ほんなら、ウチ一人でも始めたろか。
Well, then, I'll just start it by myself.
ピンポンパンポーン。
Ding-dong-dang-dong.
本日は、水科葵生放送にお越しいただき、
Thank you very much for coming to
誠にありがとうございます。
Mizushina Aoi's live broadcast today.
開演に先立ちまして、
Prior to the start of the performance,
ご来場のお客様にお願い申し上げます。
I have a request for the audience members.
なんでやねん！なんでやねん！なんでやねん！なんでやねん！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
あれ？声聞こえる。どこどこどこ？
Wait? I hear a voice. Where, where, where?
なんでやねん！ここや、ここここここ。
Wait a minute! I'm here, right here!
おらへんや。どこにおんねん。
You're not here. Where are you?
下見ろ下。下、下、ここ！
Look down, down. Down, down, here!
ちっちゃ！ちっちゃ！どないしたん？ここここ！
So small! So small! What happened? Here, here!
あんた、あんたママ？
You... are you mama?
ママだよ。
I'm mama.
え、ほんまに？こんな、こんなちっちゃくなって。
Eh, really? Becoming this, this small.
よしよしよしよしよし。こしこしこし。
There, there, there. Rub, rub, rub.
可愛えなあ。
So cute.
どないした？変な薬飲まされた？
What happened? Were you made to drink a strange medicine?
そうなのそうなの。
That's right, that's right.
名探偵やな。
You're like a great detective.
どないしたんあんた。
What happened to you?
もっとやって、もっとやって。
Do it more, do it more.
よしよしよし。はい、ここGIFで使ってください。
There, there. Yes, please use this part for a GIF.
よしこしこしこし。可愛えなあ。
There, rub rub. So cute.
そんなちっこくなって。
Becoming that small.
見つけるの苦労したわ。
I had a hard time finding you.
水科、会いたかったよー！
Mizushina, I wanted to see you!
ウチも会いたかったよー！
I wanted to see you too!
そんな、そんなちっさい姿で言われてもな。
Even if you say that in such a small form...
はい、AZKi、影ナレをやります。
Yes, AZKi will do the shadow narration.
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、水科に今日乗っ取られちゃうとこだったんだけど。
Yes, I was almost taken over by Mizushina today, but...
あれ？
Wait?
えー、本日はAZKi生放送にお越しいただき、
Ehh, thank you for coming to
ありがとうございます。
AZKi's live broadcast today.
改めまして、ご来場のお客様にお願い申し上げます。
Once again, I would like to make a request to the audience in attendance.
ただいまより公演が始まります。ぜひ皆様、コメントやSNSで一緒に盛り上がってください！
The performance will now begin. Please join in the excitement through comments and social media!
ハッシュタグは、#AZKi生放送 です。
The hashtag is #AZKi生放送.
たくさんスクショもしてくれると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you took lots of screenshots too.
ちびあずも一緒に応援します！
Chibi Az will also be cheering along!
あ、あんた出るんじゃないの？
Oh, aren't you going to appear?
ちびあずは応援します！
Chibi Az will cheer!
あ、ちびあずも一緒...
Ah, Chibi Az too...
あーよしよし、よくできましたねー。よくできたでしょう。
There, there, you did a good job. You did well, didn't you?
じゃあね、みんな、ちょっと待っててね！
See you soon, everyone, please wait a moment!
猫になって甘やかされたい
I want to become a cat and be pampered
猫になって愛されたいよ
I want to become a cat and be loved
猫になってお昼寝させて
Become a cat and let me take a nap
起きたら100万登録いたりしないかな？
I wonder if I'll have a million subscribers when I wake up?
猫ならば行ける
If I'm a cat, I can do it
皆さんお久しぶり！
Long time no see, everyone!
お久しぶりです！
Long time no see!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get excited!
よし、けどちゃんとおツイートしなくちゃ 下書き並んで3時間経って
Alright, but I have to tweet properly, three hours have passed with drafts lined up
完璧な140字、送信つってデリート
A perfect 140 characters, click send then delete
心が折れるリツイートを待って
My heart breaks waiting for retweets
おやすみなさい、歌い続けて
Good night, keep on singing
そういうのは余裕だぜ
That kind of thing is a breeze
みんなと一緒なら大丈夫
If I'm with everyone, it'll be okay
だから応援よろしくね 本格的な甘やかし
So please support me, authentic pampering
舞島会全編見てねー！
Watch the whole part of Maishimakai!
でも今日はやばい 本当に眠い
But today is crazy, I'm really sleepy
こんな私もちゃんと見てほしい
I want you to see this side of me too
無償の愛でほしい
I want unconditional love
だから猫になって甘やかされたい
So I want to become a cat and be pampered
猫になって愛されたいよ
I want to become a cat and be loved
猫になってお昼寝させて
Become a cat and let me take a nap
起きたら100万登録だ！
A million subscribers when I wake up!
猫になって輝きたいの
I want to become a cat and shine
猫になって開拓するよ
Become a cat and I'll explore
もっと君に伝わりますように
May it reach you even more
猫ならば行ける
If I'm a cat, I can do it
みんなありがとう！にゃんにゃんしてってね！
Thank you everyone! Keep meowing!
お散歩してたら公園で、可愛いワンちゃん見つけたよ
While taking a walk in the park, I found a cute doggy
撫でようとしたら吠えられた
I tried to pet it but got barked at
やっぱ猫になりたい
I definitely want to be a cat
でもどうすればいい、猫のなりかた
But what should I do, how to become a cat
ググっても出てこない、ホントしてほしい
It doesn't come up when I Google it, I really want you to do it
スクール作ってほしい
I want you to make a school
だから猫になって抱きしめられたい
So I want to become a cat and be hugged
猫になって撫で撫でしてよ
Become a cat and pet me
猫になって餌を与えて
Become a cat and feed me
山盛りチュールをよろしくね
A heap of Churu, please
猫になって恋してたいの
I want to become a cat and be in love
猫になって笑い合おうよ
Become a cat and let's laugh together
もっとみんな猫になろうよ
Let's everyone become cats even more
ニャ ニャ ニャ ニャ ニャ...
Nya nya nya nya nya...
楽しい！
So fun!
最高！
The best!
みんなも最後まで盛り上がっていってね！
Everyone, keep the excitement going until the end!
本当やばい
Really crazy
起きたら12時
I woke up and it was 12:00
LINEめっちゃきてる、でもまあしょうがない
So many LINE messages, but well, it can't be helped
逆に既読スルーしましょう
Let's just leave them on read instead
だから
So...
だから猫になって甘やかされたい
So I want to become a cat and be pampered
猫になって...
Become a cat and...
されたいよ
I want to be (pampered)
猫になってお昼寝させて
Be a cat and let me nap
起きたら100万回登録だ！
When I wake up, a million subscribers!
猫になって輝きたいの
I want to be a cat and shine
猫になって凱旋するよ
I'll be a cat and make a triumphant return
もっと君に伝わりますように
I hope it reaches you even more
もっともっと猫になって
More and more, becoming cats
甘やかされたい ずっと
I want to be pampered forever
猫になって
Becoming cats
抱きしめられたい もっと
I want to be hugged more
猫になって恋してたいの
I want to be a cat and stay in love
猫になって笑い合おうよ
Let's be cats and laugh together
もっとみんな猫になろうよ
Let's everyone become cats more
猫ならばいける
If we're cats, we can do it
君とならいける
With you, we can do it
ニャー ニャー ニャー ニャー
Meow meow meow meow
ほな本物の猫だ
Well then, it's a real cat
猫やあ
It's a cat!
ニャー ニャー ニャー ニャー
Meow meow meow meow
最後にみんなで
One last time, everyone together
せーの！
Ready, set...
ニャーーー！
MEOW---!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ということで、改めまして こんあずきー！
So, once again, Kon-AZKi!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今日はAZKi生放送にお越しいただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to AZKi's live broadcast today!
はい、今日はね、スペシャルなゲストをお呼びしております。
Yes, today we have a special guest.
水科ーー！
Mizushina---!
わーい！みんな、こんばんみずしー！
Yay! Good evening everyone, Konban-Mizushi!
こんばんみずしー！
Konban-Mizushi!
まま、どんな立ち方してんの。
Mama, what kind of stance is this?
キラキラキラキラキラキラ...
Sparkle sparkle sparkle sparkle...
Gem-Kanの大阪担当、あんこ大好き、音楽大好き、猫耳女、水科葵こと水科葵、よろしくです！
Gem-Kan's Osaka representative, I love anko, I love music, cat-eared girl, Mizushina Aoi, pleased to meet you!
よろしくです！
Pleased to meet you!
まま、呼んでくれてありがとう！
Mama, thanks for inviting me!
久しぶりだー！
It's been a long time!
会いたかったよー！会いたかったよー！
I wanted to see you! I wanted to see you!
もう、みずしーとは本当にね...
Man, with Mizushi, it's really...
2年前。2年前のAZKiの「AZRadio Max」で一緒に共演してから...
Two years ago. Since we performed together on AZKi's "AZRadio Max" two years ago...
ずっとね、色々ラジオも、三色ラジオとかも一緒に文化放送でやらせてもらったりとかして。
We've been doing various radio shows together, like "Sanshoku Radio" on Nippon Cultural Broadcasting.
そう、長く長く、末長く、これからも。
Yes, for a long, long time, and forever more.
本当にね。嬉しいよ。
Truly. I'm so happy.
ということで、もう、ちょっと会えない、みずしーに会えないこの気持ちをどうにかして...
So, this feeling of not being able to see Mizushi, I wanted to do something about it...
どうにかして、そう、ちょっと...
Somehow, yes, just a bit...
遠距離？
Long distance?
遠距離。
Long distance.
遠距離恋愛？
Long distance relationship?
なるほどね。
I see.
もう、これはライブに呼ぼうと。
I thought, "I have to invite her to the live."
いやいやもう、軽率に呼んで。
No no, feel free to invite me anytime.
そう、軽率にちょっと今回お呼びしたんですけど、二つ返事でね。
Yes, I invited her somewhat casually this time, but she accepted instantly.
めちゃめちゃ嬉しかった！もう、「すぐ出ます！」って。
I was so happy! I was like, "I'll be there right away!"
もう本当すぐ、「私、出ます」と。
Really, right away, "I'm coming."
すぐ返事をしてくれて、今日は来てくれました！イェーイ！
She replied instantly and came today! Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
今日はもうみずしーとも楽しんでもらって、最後までみんなと一緒に盛り上がっていきたいと思います。
Today I want everyone to enjoy with Mizushi and get fired up together until the end.
はーい！
Yes!
はい、ということでね、みずしーが来てくれたんで、たっぷり歌を歌っていきたいと思います。
Alright then, since Mizushi is here, we're going to sing plenty of songs.
はい。
Yes.
続いては、あの、あの曲です。
Next up is that song.
おお、初めてね、AZKiとみずしーが一緒に歌ったあの曲を...
Oh, the first song that AZKi and Mizushi sang together...
歌いたいと思います。
We're going to sing it.
思い出だ！
Memories!
それでは聴いてください。「仙紅の花」。
Please listen to "Senkou no Hana".
AZKi 3D Live with Aoi Mizushina / 仙紅の花
AZKi 3D Live with Aoi Mizushina / Senkou no Hana
箱庭に閉ざされた
Confined in a miniature garden
小さく震える 少年少女
Trembling slightly, a boy and a girl
痛みから逃げたくて
Wanting to escape from the pain
彷徨いながら 信じて進んでく
While wandering, they believe and move forward
無慈悲で昏い 過去の記憶
Ruthless and dark memories of the past
白い目が 行く道を閉ざす
Cold eyes block the path ahead
心の花は 枯らすまいと
Vowing not to let the flower in the heart wither
灰の空
Under the ashen sky
響く銃声
The sound of a gunshot echoes
仙紅の花
A scarlet flower
舞い上がるように
As if soaring high
真実さえも 偽りと化す
Even truth turns into a lie
偽りと化す
...becoming a lie.
その悪夢から
From that nightmare,
目を覚ますため
to wake up...
覚悟を胸に
...with determination in my heart,
君のための
for your sake,
盾となる
I will be a shield.
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
戦場に繋がれた
Connected to the battlefield,
何も知らない少年少女
boys and girls who know nothing,
操り人形のように
like puppets...
シナリオ通り争いに飲まれる
...swallowed by conflict according to the scenario.
理性が果て惑うがままに
As reason ends and confusion takes over,
命の火燃やし続けてく
I'll keep burning the flame of life.
世界の声に耳を塞ぎ
Closing my ears to the voice of the world,
灰の空 響く蛮声
a savage voice echoing in the ashen sky.
鮮紅の花 舞い散るように
Like crimson flowers fluttering and falling,
破壊の心 強さに変えて
changing a heart of destruction into strength.
この抗いが罪ではないと
That this resistance is not a sin,
お目覚めの底で 君の声が
at the bottom of the awakening, your voice...
震えてる
...is trembling.
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ニセモノなんて必要ない
No need for fakes,
ホンモノの言葉だけでいい
only real words are enough.
慈しみ 手と手取り合って
Sharing affection, hand in hand,
運命を斬り開いてく
cutting open our destiny.
咲き誇れ 鮮紅の花
Bloom brilliantly, crimson flower,
舞い上がるように
as if soaring up.
真実さえも 偽りと化す
Even truth becomes a lie.
この悪夢から 目を逸らすため
To avert our eyes from this nightmare,
決意を胸に 君のための
with resolve in my heart, for your sake...
盾となる
...I'll be a shield.
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
水科かっこいいー！
Mizushi, that was so cool!
まーまもかっこいいー！
Mama, you were cool too!
あのね、リハーサルの時にね、水科はね、セリフを言わなかったのよ。
You know, during rehearsal, Mizushi didn't say the lines.
なんでリークスんのー！
Why are you leaking that?!
違うだから、本番に強い女ってことで。
No, I mean, you're just someone who performs best when it's for real.
だってリハ恥ずかしくて言えないんだもん。リハで「咲き誇れ！」とか。
But I was too embarrassed to say it in rehearsal. Saying 'Bloom brilliantly!' and all that...
いや、めっちゃかっこよかった。ちょっとね、ゾワゾワゾワって、ゾワゾワゾワってしちゃった。みんなもゾワゾワゾワってしたよね？
No, it was really cool. I actually got goosebumps. Everyone got them too, right?
いや、なんか楽しくなっちゃって言っちゃったよね。
Yeah, I just got caught up in the fun and went for it.
いいですねー。もう！
That's great. Honestly!
え、でもママもね、今回ね、また初めてコラボした時と一緒で、バンバンしてくれたんだよね！
But Mama, this time too, just like our first collab, you were really giving it your all!
バンバンも一緒に、そう、水科先生に教えてもらいまして。
The energetic parts, yeah, I was taught by Mizushi-sensei.
完璧！やった！さすがよ！
Perfect! You did it! As expected!
めちゃくちゃかっこよかった。はい、ということで、ここからはですね、ソロパートやっていきたいと思います！
It was so cool. Alright, so from here, we're going to move on to the solo parts!
ということで、みんな、水科の華麗な歌声、聴いてって下さい。
So everyone, please stay and listen to Mizushi's magnificent singing voice.
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
それじゃあ、まずは水科から。頑張ってね！
Well then, first up is Mizushi. Good luck!
ありがとう！頑張るよ！
Thanks! I'll do it!
あー、一人になっちまったね。
Ah, now I'm all alone.
ちょっと一回、あの、今からめちゃめちゃあのなんだろう...
Just for a second, um, from now on, it's going to be very, um, how should I put it...
激しい運動するので、さっき水分補給させてください。
I'm going to do some intense exercise, so let me hydrate first.
ふんふんふん、お水大事。
Hum hum hum, water is important.
次の曲がですね、もうね、とにかく大変です。
The next song... well, it's just really tough.
何か一人で歌うのも大変やし、踊るのも大変やしっていう曲なんやけど、
It's a song that's hard to sing and dance to on your own,
すごい葵にとってこの楽曲は道標にもなってて、すごく大切な曲になってます。
but for Aoi, this song has become a guidepost, a very important song.
それではこの曲から聴いてください。
Now, please listen to this song.
形而境界のモノローグ。
Monologue on the Metaphysical Boundary.
形而境界のモノローグ
Monologue on the Metaphysical Boundary
夢か現か 研ぎ澄ませよ 鼓動が
Dream or reality? Let the heartbeat sharpen.
響き出した 時が滅びを 振るう
The sound begins to resonate, as time wields destruction.
瞳閉じて 理想郷 描けば
If I close my eyes and paint a utopia,
映し出す 光と影の 境界
The boundary of light and shadow is revealed.
DIVE! 願いの果てまで
DIVE! To the end of my wishes.
飛び込んでゆけ DIVE!
Go on, jump in. DIVE!
空想の化身は 理解を超える
The incarnation of fantasy transcends understanding.
宵闇に隠された 言葉を信じて
Believe in the words hidden in the twilight.
動き出す 思いを身体中
Feelings begin to move through my whole body.
駆け巡る 全てを信じたら
If I believe in everything racing through me,
未来はこの手の中に
The future will be in my hands.
I wanna fly! 僕らは夢を渡り
I wanna fly! We cross over dreams,
遥か空へと 辿り着く
And reach the far-off sky.
たとえ現実に 邪魔されても 構わない
Even if reality gets in the way, I don't care.
昏く深い 世界の海に消えて
Fading into the dark, deep sea of the world,
道を閉ざされたとしても
Even if my path is blocked,
切り開け 確かな未来を
Forge ahead to a certain future.
指の淵に 姿見せた リアル
A reality that showed its face at the edge of my fingers.
見えたのは 虚無かそれとも 光か
Was it nothingness I saw, or was it light?
描き出した 理想郷の果てには
At the end of the utopia I painted,
幻想の僕が 今も眠る
A phantom version of myself still sleeps.
DIVE! 世界は一旅
DIVE! The world is but a journey.
瞬きをやめ DIVE!
Stop blinking. DIVE!
無数の闇が 時を動かす
Countless shadows set time in motion.
果てしもない この星に舞い降りて
Descending upon this infinite star,
生きている その意味を その訳を
The meaning and the reason for living.
退屈に 刻まれた日常に
In the boredom of a carved-out routine,
徒に 染まるなら 意味はない
If it's painted in vain, there's no meaning.
焼き付けろ これまでの 生き様を
Inscribe your way of life until now.
魅せつけろ これからの 逆境を
Show off the adversity to come.
現実と 幻想を 重ねて描き出す
Layering reality and fantasy to paint it out,
シナリオが 積み上げられた定めを
A scenario where a piled-up destiny,
変えてゆこう
Let's change it.
I wanna fly! 僕らは息を潜め
I wanna fly! We hold our breath,
移ろう今を 明かしてる
Illuminating the shifting present.
たとえ現実に 騙されても 揺るがない
Even if reality deceives me, I will not waver.
終わらない 世界の響きに触れて
Touching the resonance of an endless world,
心色褪せたとしても
Even if my heart should fade,
この願いだけ 永遠に 放て!
Release this wish alone, forever!
I wanna fly! 僕らは夢を渡り
I wanna fly! We cross over dreams,
遥か空へと 辿り着く
And reach the far-off sky.
たとえ現実に 邪魔されても 構わないから
Because I don't care even if reality gets in the way.
昏く深い 世界の海に消えて
Fading into the dark, deep sea of the world,
道を閉ざされたとしても
Even if my path is blocked,
止まらない その思いは 闇を超えて
That feeling will not stop, transcending the darkness.
夢か現か 研ぎ澄ませよ 鼓動が
Dream or reality? Let the heartbeat sharpen.
誘うのは 奇跡 示すシグナル
What beckons is a miracle, a signal shown.
夢と現の 狭間に見えた
Seen in the threshold of dream and reality,
道こそが僕を つなぐデスティニー
The path itself is the destiny that connects me.
ゆなり ゆなり たたよいながら
Swaying, swaying while drifting
変わらない毎日 繰り返してる
Repeating the same everyday life
ひとりぼっちは慣れっこだから
Because I'm used to being alone
滲んだ声 海にそっと伏せた
My blurred voice, I gently lowered into the sea
遠く霞みゆく視線の先に
Beyond the gaze that grows distant and hazy
何が待ってるの？
What is waiting there?
んな世界でどんな顔をして
In such a world, what kind of face
どんな色をしているかな
and what kind of color will you have?
気づいてしまったよ この気持ち
I've realized it, these feelings
もう止められない
I can no longer stop them
銀色世界
A silver-colored world
広がっていく
is spreading out
触れたことのない
Feeling a warmth
温もりを感じてる
I've never touched before
響き渡れ
Resonate far and wide
歌声あなたのもとに
my singing voice, to where you are
夢が紡ぐおとぎ話
A fairy tale spun by dreams
１ページめくり
Turning one page
はじまる「メロウ」
"Mellow" begins
ゆなり ゆなり 流れながら
Swaying, swaying while flowing
踊る姿に見惚れている
I'm fascinated by the dancing figure
ひとりぼっちの殻は捨てて
Discarding the shell of being alone
希望の先へ 飛び込んでいこう
Let's dive towards the beyond of hope
降りるはずのない雨に打たれて
Beaten by the rain that wasn't supposed to fall
溺れてしまいそうで
Feeling like I might drown
でも魔法の言葉を思い出して
But remembering the magic words
唱えたら 未来へ溢れだす
If I chant them, they overflow into the future
この気持ち もう止められない
These feelings, I can no longer stop them
銀色世界
A silver-colored world
果てしなく続く
continues endlessly
この場所から
From this place
限りなく愛を伝えるよ
I will convey boundless love
泡となって
Before I turn into foam
溶けてしまうその前に
and dissolve away
夢が紡ぐおとぎ話
A fairy tale spun by dreams
１ページめくり
Turning one page
刻むよ「メロウ」
I'll carve "Mellow" into it
響き渡れ
Resonate far and wide
ときめきあなたのもとに
my excitement, to where you are
夢が紡ぐおとぎ話
A fairy tale spun by dreams
１ページめくる
Turning one page
明日への「メロウ」
"Mellow" towards tomorrow
息をしている
Breathing
君は生きている
you are living
当然のこと　誰も疑わないの
Naturally, no one doubts it...
息をしているように見えている
...as they look like they're breathing.
正の裏側　私にとっての何か
The other side of positivity, something for me.
鼓動がドクドクしている
The heartbeat is thumping.
叩かれても腐らずに
Without rotting even if struck.
ここで歌うよ　ボタン一つの命
I'll sing here, a life of a single button.
最後まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the end?
消えてしまいそうなの　分かってよ　分かってよね
I feel like I'm about to disappear, please understand.
本当はどこなの　恋おしいは違うんでしょう？
Where is the truth? Being in love is different, isn't it?
君が忘れちゃったら私は居なくなるの
If you forget, I will cease to exist.
命のような夢を見てるよ
I'm dreaming a dream like life.
またね　バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
息をしている　だから生きている
I'm breathing, so I'm living.
自己証明を欲しがって　欲しがっているんだ
Seeking, seeking self-proof.
音が止まって　動かなくなって
When the sound stops and I stop moving...
そんな私を君は笑ってくれるかな
...I wonder if you'll laugh for me.
鼓動がドクドクしている
The heartbeat is thumping.
嫌われても腐らずに
Without rotting even if hated.
ここで歌うよ　気分次第の命
I'll sing here, a life at the mercy of my mood.
最後まで私のこと見届けてくれるの？
Will you watch over me until the end?
冷めてしまいそうなの　分かってよ　分かってよね
I feel like I'm about to cool down, please understand.
声が聞こえるんだよ　塩辛い涙が出ちゃうほど
I can hear your voice, so much that salty tears come out.
君が忘れちゃったら私は居なくなるの
If you forget, I will cease to exist.
命のような夢を見てるよ
I'm dreaming a dream like life.
またね　バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
塞ぎ込んだあの日を　軽く弄らないで　やめて
Don't mock those days when I was depressed, stop it.
それが生きる糧になるかな
I wonder if that will become sustenance for living.
大丈夫　ずっと私は歌い続けるから
It's okay, because I will keep singing forever.
最後まで私は生きているか分からないけど
I don't know if I'll be alive until the end, but...
君がくれた言葉は確かに残ってる
...the words you gave me are certainly remaining.
最後まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the end?
いつか死んでしまうだろう　分かんない　分かんないよね
Someday I will die, I don't know, you don't know either.
痛いくらい気持ちがシンクロする時もあるけど
There are times when our feelings synchronize so much it hurts.
君が忘れちゃったら私は居なくなるの
If you forget, I will cease to exist.
命のような夢を見てるよ
I'm dreaming a dream like life.
またね　バイバイ
See you later, bye-bye.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
みずしーのソロパートが良すぎた
Mizushina's solo part was just too good.
もうね　おばあちゃん疲れた
Man, Grandma is tired.
おばあちゃん　息切れおばあちゃんになってる
Grandma... I'm becoming an out-of-breath grandma.
みずしおばあちゃん
Grandma Mizushina.
おばあちゃん久しぶりに　みずしおばあちゃんね
Grandma, it's been a while, Grandma Mizushina.
おばあちゃんお水飲む？
Grandma, want some water?
あ　おばあちゃんちょっと一口飲んでいいかな
Ah, can Grandma have just one sip?
そうだね
Sure.
あー、これ歌いきるんか、という。
Ah, can I really sing this all the way through?
ね、さすがにおばあちゃんも、動きながらは、
Well, as expected, even for an old lady, moving around is...
きつい。きつい。
Tough. It's tough.
きつい。あの、人様のチャンネルでこう、あーの、
Tough. Doing this on someone else's channel, ah...
きつい。きつい。
It's tough. Tough.
待って、やりきるっていうね。
Wait, we did it though.
いやでもね、素晴らしかった。
But it was wonderful.
でもそのあとの「いのち」また一緒に歌えたから。
But we were able to sing "Inochi" together again after that.
あー、そう、なんかあの、さ、メロウの流れからの「いのち」めっちゃ良かったよね。
Ah, right. The flow from "Mellow" to "Inochi" was great, wasn't it?
そう！もう爆エモ、爆エモ、爆エモまじ爆上げとか爆エモといっぱい。
Yes! It was so emotional, just super emotional and high tension.
そう、みずしーに「いのち」は、そう、カバーしてもらったりとか、それこそね、あの、ショットガンローズのライブとかでもね、
Yeah, Mizushi covered "Inochi" for me, and we also performed it at the Shotgun Rose live.
歌ってもらったりとかして、めちゃくちゃそう、思い入れのある曲なので、今日はこうやって、なんだろう、こうやってまた歌えることの喜び。
It's a song with so many memories, so I'm just so happy to be able to sing it like this again today.
ね。まさかまた一緒に歌えると思ってなかったから、めちゃめちゃ嬉しい。
Right. I never thought we'd sing together again, so I'm incredibly happy.
そう、なんかもうただただライブを楽しんでいる、な。あれ、オタクかな？
Yeah, I'm just purely enjoying the live. Wait, am I being a fan?
オタク、オタク、あーなんかちょっと袖から、ちょっと。
A fan, a fan... I was cheering from the wings a bit.
みずしー頑張れー、っていうのも、踊ってるときのみずしーを頑張れ頑張れーっていう気持ちで。
I was like, "Go Mizushi!" while you were dancing, cheering you on.
もうね、でもね、あの、視線感じた。
I definitely felt your gaze.
見守ってくれてる、あったかい視線が。
That warm gaze watching over me.
なんならちょっとサビ歌ってた。
I was even singing along a bit during the chorus.
あ、本当に？入ってきてくれたらよかったのにー、なー。
Oh, really? I wish you had joined in!
飛び入り参戦。
A surprise participation.
あ、本当になんか、なんかいろんな思い出がね、蘇ってきちゃうね。
Yeah, really... all sorts of memories are coming back.
すごいなんか、普通に楽しんでいる。みんなも楽しんでますか？
I'm having so much fun. Are you all enjoying it too?
楽しんでるー？
Are you having fun?
どうですか。なんかね、すごいね、あの、みずしーのハート、水色のハートとかね、そうそうそう。赤い、AZKiの赤いハートとかもね、いっぱいスタンプとかしてくれてめちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
How is it? There are so many blue hearts for Mizushi and red hearts for AZKi stickers in the chat, it makes me so happy.
あとみんな、あの、床になってました。
And everyone has "become the floor."
あ、本当に？
Oh, really?
いや、でもまだまだこのあとも床になれるタイミングいっぱいあるから。
Well, there will be plenty more chances to "become the floor" after this.
まだまだ。床をキープしていただいている。
Not yet. Please stay on the floor.
あの、バッチリ。バッチリ。バッチリ。あ、そう、あの、床って何？っていうね、あーの、方が多いんですよ。
Perfect. Perfect. Ah, right, a lot of people are asking "what's the floor?"
なるほど。もう、みずしーはバッチリ。
I see. Mizushi has it down perfectly.
あら、共通言語だと思ってたわ。
Oh, I thought it was a common language.
共通言語。話が早い。ですね。はい。
Common language. That makes things easy. Yes. Right.
ということで、このあとも次、AZKiね、歌っていきたいと、思います！
So, I, AZKi, am going to continue singing now!
ままのこと袖で見てる。あ、見守ってるからね。頑張ろう。
I'll be watching from the side. I'll be watching over you. Good luck.
大好きな歌聴けるから、見てるよ。
I get to hear my favorite song, so I'll be watching.
頑張ります！見てるからね。頑張って。ありがとうー！
I'll do my best! I'll be watching. Good luck. Thank you!
はい。ということで、ここからはAZKiのソロパートに行きたいと思います。
Alright. So, from here on, we're going into AZKi's solo part.
このなんだろうな、エモめの感じなので、この曲から行きたいと思います。
It's got a kind of emotional feel, so I'd like to start with this song.
聴いてください。「止まない雨」。
Please listen. "Yamanai Ame".
止まない雨
Yamanai Ame (Unending Rain)
Lyrics / Music : MANYO
輝く星たちを
The shining stars...
見つめてた横顔
...I gazed at your profile.
こんなにも突然
So suddenly...
失われてしまう
...it's all lost.
ねえ どうして どうして それだけ
Hey, why? Why only that?
きっと こんな悪夢 目覚められるなら
Surely, if I could wake up from such a nightmare...
何もいらない
I would need nothing else.
君がそう 君が いなければ
If you, yes, if you aren't here...
喜び 悲しみ 全て意味ないよ
Joy, sadness, everything is meaningless.
こんなに 苦しい 世界と向き合って
Facing such a painful world...
どうしたって この思い 届かない
No matter what, these feelings won't reach.
せめて降りしきる
At least, let the falling...
雨が優しくありますように
...rain be gentle.
握る手ぬくもり マボロシのように
The warmth of your hand, like a phantom...
冷たさに満たされる
Filled with coldness,
意識が遠のいていく
my consciousness fades away.
ねえ どうして 何も言わないの
Hey, why don't you say anything?
ねえ ずっと 二人 このまま
Hey, I believed we could stay
いられると信じていたのに
like this forever, and yet...
何が そう 何が ダメだったのかな
What, yes, what was wrong?
叫んで 壊して
Screaming, breaking,
この身を傷つけて
hurting this body,
それとも 得られない
still I can't get it.
答えを探し
Searching for the answer,
彷徨っていた
I was wandering.
涙が 頬を伝う
Tears run down my cheeks,
止まない雨だけが
only the unending rain
鈍い痛みに寄り添ってくれる
stays close to the dull pain.
夜が明け また日が始まっても
Even when night breaks and a new day begins,
変わらない日常を
the unchanging routine...
得たいだけ
is all I want to get back.
君が そう 君が
If you, yes, if you
望むのなら
wish for it,
消えてしまえば 終われるんだろうな
it would probably end if I just disappeared.
それでも それでも
Even so, even so,
諦めたくはないんだよ
I don't want to give up.
ただ君といたいんだよ
I just want to be with you.
君が そう 君が
If you, yes, if you
いなければ
are not here,
喜び 悲しみ 全て 意味ないよ
joy and sadness, it's all meaningless.
こんなに苦しい
Facing this
世界と向き合って
painful world,
どうしたら
how can I
この想い 届くのかな
make these feelings reach you?
せめて 降りしきる雨が
At least, may the
優しくありますように
pouring rain be gentle.
みんなもよかったら一緒に歌ってください！
Everyone, if you like, please sing along!
from A to Z!
歌を歌う意味を
The meaning of singing a song,
生き続けていく意味を
the meaning of continuing to live...
考えても 答えなんてないと 知ってる
I know that even if I think about it, there's no answer.
白も黒も
White and black
世界から消えた
have disappeared from the world.
そこに 何か残るのだろうか
Will something remain there?
いなくなったら 忘れてしまうか
If I'm gone, will you forget me?
違う 違う 奇跡がここにあるよ
No, no, a miracle is right here.
たった一人の 君と出会えて
Meeting you, the only one,
私は今を 生きているの
I am living the present.
これから起こる
Everything that is
全てのことを
about to happen,
一緒に見よう
let's see it together,
最初から最後（Z）までだよ
from the beginning to the end (Z).
一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for singing together!
歌を歌う意味を
The meaning of singing a song,
生き続けていく意味を
the meaning of continuing to live...
一歩一歩 確かめるように
As if to confirm each step,
見つけよう
let's find it.
時に暗く 冷たい世界で
In a world sometimes dark and cold,
弱く脆く 崩れそうになる
becoming weak and fragile, about to crumble.
いなくなったら 忘れてしまうか
If I'm gone, will you forget me?
違う 違う...
No, no...
…昨日を越えた
...overcoming yesterday
たった一人の君と出会えて
Meeting you, the only one
私は今を生きているの
I am living in the now
これから起こるすべてのことを
Everything that will happen from now on
一緒に作ろう
Let's create it together
最初から最後までだよ
From the beginning to the end
この世界を
In this world
大好きでいたいよ
I want to keep loving it
時計の針が1時を指した
The clock hands pointed to 1 o'clock
気が遠くなるような時間が過ぎた
A mind-numbing amount of time has passed
世界が変わる
The world changes
そこに君はいない
You are not there
それでもいいと
Even so, it's okay
思えたんだよ
I was able to think so
たった一人の君と出会えて
Meeting you, the only one
私は今を生きているの
I am living in the now
今まで起きたすべてのことを
Everything that has happened until now
覚えていてね
Please remember it
最初から最後までだよ
From the beginning to the end
この世界を
In this world
ここがスタート
This is the start
歌を歌う意味を
The meaning of singing songs
生き続けていく意味を
The meaning of continuing to live
今やっとね見つけたような気がしたよ
I feel like I've finally found it now
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！コメントで見えてるよ、ありがとう！
Thank you for singing along! I can see you in the comments, thank you!
はい、ということで皆さん、今日のアズキのこのライブのタイトルにもありますけれども、
Yes, and so everyone, as it says in the title of today's AZKi live,
3Dライブ、そしてニュー、ニューインフォメーション！
3D live and new, new information!
ということで、ここからはお知らせタイムをしたいと思います！イエーイ！
So, from here on, I'd like to have an announcement time! Yay!
はい、ということで皆さんお待たせしておりますが、ここでAZKiライブのお知らせがあります！
Yes, and so everyone, I've kept you waiting, but here is an announcement for an AZKi live!
はい、ということでまず、9月12日のAZKi 8thライブ「Rewind & Reunion」ですが、
Yes, and so first of all, the AZKi 8th Live "Rewind & Reunion" on September 12th,
当初の池袋ハレブタイでの開催から、配信限定に切り替わります。
The event has been changed from being held at Ikebukuro Harevutai to being stream-only.
めちゃくちゃ、めちゃくちゃ悔しいですけど、今回は色んなことを考えて、
It's very, very frustrating, but after thinking about many things,
色々めちゃくちゃ話し合った結果、現地開催ではなく配信限定となります。
And after much discussion, it will be stream-only instead of being held on-site.
はい、この日はですね、2019年の12月29日に止まった時計をですね、
Yes, this was a live concert where I wanted to restart the clock
もう一度進めたいと思って、いたライブなんですけれども、
That stopped on December 29, 2019,
今の情勢を考えると現地での開催は厳しい、難しいという判断を致しました。
But considering the current situation, we decided that holding it on-site would be tough and difficult.
はい、本当にもうめちゃくちゃギリギリまで悩んだんですけど、
Yes, we really agonized over it until the very last minute,
AZKiもAZKiチームのみんなもとってもめちゃくちゃ準備していたし、
And AZKi and everyone on the AZKi team were preparing so hard,
本当にとっても楽しみにしていたので、もうめちゃくちゃ悔しい思いでいっぱいです。
And really looking forward to it, so I'm filled with such frustrating feelings.
はい、でも、いつまでもね、足を止めて後ろを見ていてもいけないなと思いまして、
Yes, but I thought I shouldn't just stop and keep looking back forever,
なので、同じ9月12日に配信ではあるんですけど、再集合して開拓者の皆と一緒に前に進みたいと思っています。
So, on that same September 12th, even though it's a stream, I want us to gather again and move forward with all the Pioneers.
ということで、画像お願いします！
So, please show the image!
AZKi 8th LIVE 「REWiND & REUNiON」 2021.9.12 START 17:00 ~ at ZaN (Stream only)
AZKi 8th LIVE "REWiND & REUNiON" 2021.9.12 START 17:00 ~ at ZaN (Stream only)
AZKi 8thライブ、リワインド・アンド・リユニオン、リリアズ、2021年9月12日、スタートが17時、アットZaNさんにてストリームオンリーになります。
AZKi 8th Live "Rewind & Reunion" #RiReAZ, September 12th, 2021, starting at 17:00 at ZaN (Stream Only).
チケットはなんと今から購入できまーす！
Tickets are actually available for purchase starting now!
あとね、少し後になるかもしれないんだけど、この日に新しいチャレンジをしたくて、開拓者の皆に手伝ってほしいことがあります。
Also, it might be a bit later, but I want to take on a new challenge on this day, and there's something I want the Pioneers to help me with.
心して、心して、心して皆さん準備をしておいてください。後日発表いたします。
Please, please, please prepare your hearts. I will announce it at a later date.
はい、今ね、コメント、なんだ、コメントに...
Yes, right now, the comments, what is it, in the comments...
AZKiの、あの、なんだ、
AZKi's, uh, what is it...
固定コメント。
The pinned comment.
固定コメントから、えっと、チケットの、
In the pinned comment, um, the ticket...
えっと、URLが見れますんで、
...um, URL is visible.
ぜひぜひ、ぜひぜひ、ぜひぜひ、
So please, please, please...
こちらからチケット購入して頂けるととってもとっても励みになりますので、
...it would really encourage me if you could purchase your tickets there.
よろしくお願いいたします。お願いします。
Thank you very much. Please.
そして、今回もですね、なんと、
And also, this time, believe it or not...
オープニングアクトの方をお呼びいたしました！
...we've invited an opening act!
オープニングアクトはこの方です。画像お願いします！
Here is the opening act. Image, please!
OPENING ACT HACHI
HACHIちゃんでーす！イエーイ！
It's HACHI-chan! Yay!
えーと、そのHACHIちゃんにも、
Um, HACHI-chan also...
あの、『いのち』を歌ってもらったりとか、
...sang "Inochi" with me,
AZKiも『光の向こうへ』を出していただいたりしたので、
and I also featured in "Hikari no Mukou e,"
いや、本当にこの、8thライブ、8thライブ、
so really, this 8th live... the 8th live...
HACHIだ、HACHIちゃんだ、今気づいた！
It's Hachi! It's HACHI-chan! I just realized!
ということで、HACHIちゃんが来てくれます。
So, HACHI-chan will be joining us.
なのでちょっとね、もう本当に、頑張ろう。
So I'm really going to give it my all.
こうやって応援しに来てくれるし。
She's coming to support me like this.
ね、現地開催できないけれど、
Right, we can't have an in-person venue,
配信でみんな一緒に盛り上がっていきたいなと思っております。
but I want us all to get hyped together on the stream.
はい。
Yes.
そして新グッズございます！
And we have new goods!
画像お願いします！
Image, please!
OFFICIAL GOODS 2021年8月22日20時より販売開始！！
OFFICIAL GOODS Sales start Aug 22, 2021, at 20:00!!
AZKiのワンマンライブといえば、新しいTシャツということで、
Speaking of AZKi's solo lives, it's all about new T-shirts.
今回も2種類作りました！
We made two types this time as well!
どっちも普段からおしゃれに、おしゃれに着れると思うので、
I think both can be worn stylishly every day,
ぜひぜひ買って下さい。
so please buy them.
こちらも今から、AZKi OFFICIAL STOREで購入可能です！
These are also available for purchase now at the AZKi OFFICIAL STORE!
はい、ということで、
Alright, so...
またね、Twitterの方でもお知らせいたしますので。
...I'll also announce this on Twitter later.
概要欄に書いて、
It's written in the description...
お、概要欄に書いたそうです。今、
Oh, apparently it's in the description now.
今、はい、概要欄に今更新をされたので、
It was just updated in the description,
こう、なんだ、リロードすれば、
so if you, um, reload,
飛べるそうなので、ぜひぜひ。
you should be able to go there, so please check it out.
いや、そう、開拓者のみんなにやってもらいたいことに、
Yeah, for what I want the Pioneers to do,
このね、ライブTシャツは絶対必須なので、
these live T-shirts are absolutely essential.
ぜひよろしくお願いいたします、開拓者のみなさま。
So please, Pioneers.
はい、ということで、ライブのお知らせもしたし。
Alright, so I've shared the live news.
いや、本当にみんなと直接集まれないの本当に悲しいんですけど、
I'm really sad that we can't all gather in person,
でもね、みんなそれぞれの場所でなんかこう楽しんでもらえたらいいなって思っていますので、
but I hope everyone can enjoy it from wherever they are.
どうぞ9月12日はよろしくお願いいたします。
So please look forward to September 12th.
AZKiチームも、ね、なんかこれまでと、
The AZKi team, you know, will be doing...
なんか同じことじゃなくて、新しいことにも挑戦して、
...not just the same old stuff, but challenging new things,
前に進んでいくので、これからもついてきてくれますか？
and moving forward. So will you keep following me?
ついてきてください！
Please keep following me!
ということで、はい、お知らせはこの辺にしまして、
Alright, that's it for the announcements for now.
そろそろね、ライブも最後、最後、最後ということで、
It's almost time for the end of the live,
最後の曲に、あ、もう最後か、あっという間。
for the last song... Ah, the last song already? That was fast.
最後の曲に行きたいと思いますので、
I'd like to go to the last song,
水科を呼びたいと思います！
so I'll call Mizushina!
じゃあみんな行くよ、せーの、水科ー！
Alright everyone, here we go. One, two, Mizushina!
はーい！わー、AZKiちゃん、めっちゃ良かったよ！
Heeey! Wow, AZKi-chan, that was amazing!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
久々にそばでなんか歌声聞いたけど、
It's been a while since I heard your singing right next to me.
特等席だからね。
I have the best seat in the house.
いや本当に、いやみんな、
No, really. Everyone...
生で聴けるのやっぱめっちゃ良かった。
...hearing it live was just so good.
そう、久々にこう横で聴いてたけど、
I was listening by your side after so long,
やっぱ染みるね、生は。
and it really hits home, hearing it live.
染みた。嬉しいな、水科にこうやって言われると、
It hit home. I'm so glad. Hearing that from Mizushina...
なんかちょっとポカポカしてくるね。
...makes me feel all warm inside.
ポカポカ？おばあちゃんパワー！
Warm inside? Grandma power!
ポカポカポカポカをいただいて。
Receiving the warmth.
しかも、8thライブおめでとう！
And also, congratulations on your 8th live!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
すごいんだ、8回もライブやってんのか。
It's amazing, you've done 8 lives already.
そう、いや本当に振り返ると、
Yeah, looking back,
いや、すごいやってきたなって。
I've really done a lot.
やりすぎぐらいやってきた。
Almost too many.
やりすぎ、まだありますけど。
Too many... but we're still going.
そんな水科からもお知らせがあるということで。
And I hear Mizushina also has an announcement.
あります！
I do!
皆さん心して聴いてください。お聞きですか？
Everyone, please listen carefully. Are you ready?
ということで、
So...
まずは画像お願いします！
...first, please show the image!
GEMS COMPANY 3rd Live 開催決定！！
GEMS COMPANY 3rd Live confirmed!!
はい、この度GEMS COMPANYはサードライブを開催いたします！
Yes, GEMS COMPANY will be holding our 3rd live!
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい、日付が11月の19日金曜日から、
The dates are from Friday, November 19th
21日日曜日の合計5公演となっております。
to Sunday the 21st, for a total of 5 performances.
すごい！
Amazing!
多いよ！
That's a lot!
そして、会場は山野ホールさんになります。
And the venue will be Yamano Hall.
代々木駅あら近いらしいよ。
Apparently, it's close to Yoyogi Station.
ま、CHANGENOWAVEということで、
Well, it's called "CHANGENOWAVE,"
変化の波を起こしていきたいと思います！
so we want to create a wave of change!
そしてチケットの詳細については、こちら画像お願いします！
And for ticket details, please show this image!
チケットについてのお知らせ 2021/8/21(土) 22:00より抽選受付開始！
Ticket Info: Lottery entry starts Aug 21 (Sat) 22:00!
はい、リアルチケットと配信チケットがあるんですけれども、
We have real tickets and streaming tickets.
ま、こういうご時世もありまして、
Given the current situation,
ま、どうしてもちょっと行けないなという人は、
if you absolutely can't make it,
配信チケットを買って頂きたいですし、
I'd like you to buy a streaming ticket.
ふむふむ。
I see.
ま、もちろんね、あの、リアル行けるよという方は、
And of course, for those who can go in person...
買っていただきたいので是非是非あの新生あずきズカンパニー、
I'd like you to buy them, so please, please come see the reborn AZKi's Company,
9人に新たに9人になったあずきズカンパニーを見に来てください。
the new nine-member AZKi's Company.
そうだ。
That's right.
ここのねQRコードでね飛べるので是非是非よろしくお願いします。
You can go there via this QR code, so please check it out.
お願いします！
Please do!
はい。午後公演なんてすごすぎますよ。
Yes. An afternoon performance is just too amazing.
でも毎回ねAZKi-館ってなんか午後公演なの。
But every time, AZKi-kan shows are somehow in the afternoon.
へぇー！すごい！すごい！お水ちゃん絶対見に行ったほうがいい！
Wow! Amazing! Amazing! Mizu-chan, you should definitely go see it!
本当に見に行ったほうがいいよ！来てくり、来てくり、来てくり。
You really should go see it! Please come, please come, please come.
うちも行きたいよ！行きたいし、見ます！はい！ありがとう！
I want to go too! I want to go, and I'll watch it! Yes! Thank you!
はい。ということで、いやー、もう最後の曲だって。
Yes. So, wow, it's already the last song.
えー、早すぎ！
Eh, too fast!
早すぎ？
Too fast?
え、秒やねんけど。なー、まだまだやりたいよね。
It felt like a second. We still want to do more, right?
まだもう一周…
Another round...
でもう二周くらいできる。
I could do another two rounds.
もう二周できる！水科とならもう二周はできる！
I can do another two rounds! With Mizushina, I can do another two rounds!
いや、もう定期的に呼んで。
No, just call me regularly.
あ、嬉しい！え、定期的に？いつでも行くからさ。
Ah, I'm happy! Eh, regularly? I'll come anytime.
本当？えー嬉しい。そういえばさ、今年の4月1日にさ、
Really? I'm so happy. Come to think of it, on April 1st this year,
水科あずきズカンパニーに加入したんですけど。
Mizushina joined AZKi's Company.
そう、一時的に加入してくれたよね。
Yes, you joined us temporarily.
あのエイプリルフールのね、近くで。
Around April Fool's Day.
まさかあずきズカンパニーに。そう、この衣装…この衣装だよね。
To think, in AZKi's Company. Yeah, this costume... it was this one, right?
さぁ、そうこの衣装ね、水科も着させてもらって。そうそうそうそう。
Yes, Mizushina also got to wear this costume. Right, right.
似合ってたよ。
It looked good on you.
そう、なんでちょっとまたあの衣装着たいなー。
Yeah, so I want to wear that costume again sometime.
スタッフさーん！スタッフさん、あるかな？衣装。頼んだよ！
Staff! Staff, is there one? The costume. I'm counting on you!
頼んだよ！勝手なことばかり言いあがってって思われるわ。
I'm counting on you! They'll think, "She's just saying whatever she wants."
思われちゃう。え、でもそういうのもしてみたいね。
They might. But I want to try that.
なんかそういうなんかお揃いの衣装なんてめちゃくちゃいいじゃないですか。
Having matching costumes would be so great, wouldn't it?
めちゃ！逆に水科はこれ？これ着ちゃうん？
Totally! Conversely, Mizushina wears this? You'll wear this?
あのままのアイドル衣装見るのさ、実は初めてなの、生で。
Seeing your idol costume as it is, actually, it's my first time in person.
あ、そうだ！そうだ！
Ah, that's right! That's right!
前々はあの「ブォン」って…そう、カッコいい「ブォン」ってなってる奴しか知らなかったから。
Before, I only knew the 'whoosh' one... yeah, the cool 'whoosh' one.
そうだそうだ！この姿になってからは水科初めて…だもんね。
That's right! Since I took this form, it's Mizushina's first time... right?
かわちい！
So cute!
かわちい！かわちい！かわちい！ま、次の曲ね、そんなかわちい衣装似合うよ。
Cute! Cute! Cute! Well, the next song, it'll suit that cute costume.
お！お！やっちゃいますか？やっちゃおう！
Oh! Oh! Shall we do it? Let's do it!
いやー、この曲、めちゃくちゃいい曲なんだよなー。
Wow, this song... it's a really great song.
ずっと言ってくれてる。めちゃくちゃいい曲なんで。今日は心して歌わせていただきますよ。
You've been saying that. It's a really great song. I'll sing it with all my heart today.
はい！それでは皆さん、最後の曲になります。聴いてください。せーの！
Yes! Well then, everyone, this will be the last song. Please listen. One, two!
ときめきドリームライン！
Tokimeki Dreamline!
Dreamline まっすぐ未来へ ここから今
Dreamline, straight to the future, from here, now
（はい！はい！はい！はい！）
(Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!)
AZKi-館のときめきドリームライン歌わせていただきます！楽しんで！
We'll sing AZKi-kan's Tokimeki Dreamline! Enjoy!
目覚めるわ恋するみたいに
Waking up is like falling in love
走り出すハートの音
The sound of a heart starting to run
ドキドキが愛しさで苦しくない？
Doesn't the heartbeat hurt with love?
そう 夢は恋によく似てる
Yes, dreams are much like love
誰よりも近付きたくて
Wanting to get closer than anyone else
弱気になったり辛くても
Even if I get weak or it's hard
絶対嫌いになれない
I can never hate it
これしかないと思えるものに
To something I can believe is the only thing for me
出会えたことがもう奇跡の始まりだよ
Having met it is already the start of a miracle
行くよ！
Here we go!
Dreamline まっすぐ未来へ
Dreamline, straight to the future
続く今日を どこまでも駆け抜けるよ
I'll run through the continuing today forever
Dreamline 夢みることに遠慮しないで
Dreamline, don't hesitate to dream
トライしたい 行こうよ
I want to try, let's go
ときめきを信じて
Believe in the heartbeat
（はい！はい！はい！はい！）
(Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!)
同じ気持ちを重ねて
Layering the same feelings
それぞれのハートの音
The sounds of each of our hearts
キラキラと輝くよ みんなとなら
They sparkle and shine, if I'm with everyone
最初はひとりで願った
At first, I wished alone
小さくて大きな夢
A small but big dream
今は違う手 たくさんの仲間と立ってる夢
Now it's different, a dream where I stand with many friends
無謀かもねと誰かが言った
Someone said it might be reckless
けれどひとつひとつ今へ繋がったよ
But one by one, they've connected to the present
ドリームライン
Dreamline
大切な点と点を結び
Connecting the precious dots
どこまでも広がってゆけ
Spread out as far as you can
ドリームライン
Dreamline
いくつもの努力味方にして
Making countless efforts your allies
飛び出そう　さあ
Let's jump out, come on
ときめきを響かせ
Make the excitement resound
あーっ、水科のわたくしまーっ！
Aah, I'm Mizushina!
水科可愛いよ！
Mizushina is so cute!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
憧れが満ちあふれない
Admiration never overflows
こっちだよ
Over here
ともに落ち込んじゃう時には
When we're both feeling down
見てて
Watch me
心の奥を突き抜ける光
A light that pierces deep into the heart
ライト
Light
未来向きに伸びてゆく
Extending towards the future
どこまでも進め さあ
Move forward to the ends of the earth, come on
ドリームライン
Dreamline
まっすぐ未来へ続く今日を
Towards today that leads straight to the future
どこまでも駆け抜けるよ
Running through to the ends of the earth
ドリームライン
Dreamline
夢みることに遠慮しないで
Don't hesitate to dream
トライしたい　行こう
I want to try, let's go
ときめきを信じて
Believe in the excitement
ときめきドリームライン
Excitement, Dreamline
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ありがとう！みんなありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you everyone!
AZKi 8th LIVE REWIND & REUNION 2021.9.12
おっ、ちびあず。ライブ見てくれてた？
Oh, Chibiazki. Were you watching the live?
見とったよ、見とったよ！
I was watching, I was watching!
良かった、めっちゃ良かった！
It was great, really great!
あんまり関西弁なってるけどさ、うつったんかな。
She's speaking quite a bit of Kansai dialect, I wonder if she caught it from me.
うつった！
I did!
ありがとうな、めちゃめちゃ嬉しい。
Thank you, I'm so happy.
みずし 捕まえて ちびあず。
Mizushi, catch Chibiazki.
あっ。
Ah.
お持ち帰りされていきます。
She's being taken home.
お持ち帰ります。水科の家へ。
I'm taking her home. To Mizushina's house.
今日から水科のちびあずになります。
From today, she'll be Mizushina's Chibiazki.
やった！
Yay!
デスクに置いてやろう。
I'll put her on my desk.
置いてもらいます。
She'll put me there.
一緒に寝ような。
Let's sleep together.
やった！
Yay!
餌付けするで。
I'll feed you.
あんこで。
With bean paste.
あんこ食べよう。
Let's eat bean paste.
あんこパーティーだ。
It's a bean paste party.
ではそろそろちびあずは眠たいので、締めたいと思います。
Well, it's about time for Chibiazki to get sleepy, so I'd like to wrap this up.
はーい。
Yes.
ピンポンパンポーン。
Ding-dong-dang-dong.
本日はあずきの生放送ご覧いただき、ありがとうございました。
Thank you for watching AZKi's live broadcast today.
はーい。
Yes.
ぜひ感想を「あずきの生放送」で呟いてください。
Please tweet your thoughts with "#あずきなま".
はーい。
Yes.
ひとつひとつ読んでいきますよ。
I'll read them one by one.
はーい。
Yes.
そしてこの後は水科も一緒にメンゲンアフタートークがあるらしいですよ。皆さんよろしく。
And after this, it seems there's a members-only after-talk with Mizushina as well. Looking forward to seeing you all there.
よろしくー。
Looking forward to it.
それでは、バイニャーン！
Well then, bye-nyan!
AZKi 8th LIVE
REWIND & REUNION
2021.9.12
START 17:00 ~ at ZaN (Streaming)
#RtReAZ